So the White House has now released a statement about the brutality of the Tyree Nichols video.
It's the lack of acknowledgement of the comprehensive context within which this takes place.
That's what's getting to me.
But just for the record, the irony makes me laugh because they're saying that this is the most brutal example that they've ever seen of policing.
And for the record, we have seen George Floyd literally choke to death in front of us.
I also just find it odd because I can't help but feel like there is something being attached to these cops who are absolutely horrible people, but are also black men.
And there's an inhumaneness being attached to them that has not been attached to the myriad of white cops before them.
That have behaved in inhumane manners.
I mean, we can also just acknowledge that we have seen inhumanity over and over again.
Like these out here lynching folks and having picnics.
Okay, the term drawing quartered, does that ring a bell?
And also, why are they announcing it like a Netflix drop?
Like it's a new versus.